

NAUSHIKHA JAYAWICKRAMA

Phone: +94 76331 6991 E-mail: hello@naushikha.com Website: naushikha.com







A GAME CHANGER.

PROFILE

Hardworking, self-motivated ambitious programmer with a keen eye for detail. Excellent track record of performance in all tasks undertaken with exceeding 4 years of cumulative industrial experience in fields such as networking, customer support and tutoring. Aiming to work in a challenging but friendly environment with a goal to become a part of a team. Secondary interest is in DevOps.

EXPERIENCE

SOFTWARE ENGINEER INTERN

SimCentric Technologies (Oct 2021 - May 2022)

• Working on SAF-TAC: a virtual reality based tactical military simulator.

SYSTEM ENGINEER

Telasis Solutions (2017 - 2019)

- System and network installation and administration.
- Server and desktop hardware configuration.

WEB DEVELOPMENT MANAGER

SEDS UOC (Jan 2021 - May 2022)

- Leading the creation and maintenance of SEDS UOC website and blog.
- Handling all the web-related technicalities of the organization.

PROJECTS

SPOTIFY WIDGET

Cloudflare Powered Middleware - 2021

- Runs as a serverless application on Cloudflare.
- Open source solution that can embed your currently playing song on Spotify in a website as a widget.
 Article Link

LIGHTER FRAMEWORK

PHP MVC Framework - 2021

- Based on the initial SLMOsys framework I designed.
- Modular and a somewhat opinionated framework but is a great lightweight framework to kickstart small PHP MVC applications. Repo Link

SEDSUOC.LK

Web and Blog Design - 2021

- Designed using pure HTML, CSS, JS and WordPress.
- As the web development manager of SEDS UOC, led the team to create and maintain the <u>website</u> and <u>blog</u>.
 Website Link | <u>Blog Link</u>

SKILLSET

- Linux, networking and system administration
- · Hardware installation, upgrading and maintennance
- Quick learning
- Problem solving
- Adaptability
- Fluent communication.

EDUCATION

University of Colombo School of Computing (2019 >>)

• Current GPA: **3.8** (out of 4.0)

BSC (HONS)
COMPUTER SCIENCE